PHUONG LE

5641 Roswell Road, Unit 103 Atlanta, GA 30342 (205) 566-2320 phuonganh.leo312@gmail.com

To whom it may concern,

Please regard this letter as my formal application. Attached is my resume containing further details of my education, experience, and skills.

For the past five years, I have worked various occupations that focus on customer service. In all the roles that I have taken, I strived to foster strong relationships with both customers and colleagues. Being Vietnamese-American, I work hard to perfect both my native and second language, which in turn polishes my communication skills. By applying strong conversational skills and clear articulation to my work, I find that I am able to build steady rapport with my clients and in turn, increase my satisfaction rate exponentially.

As of recent, I have switched career paths and began my journey in the tech industry. I am currently a student in the Georgia Tech Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp. I became interested in the tech field, specifically coding, as I have always enjoyed building things from scratch. I aspire to develop interactive, accessible, and efficient digital experiences through my projects. I also enjoy challenges that require me to work outside of my knowledge and comfort, as learning new languages and development skills are crucial to my success in this industry.

Throughout my work experience in customer service I have learned to build solid foundations with others and tailor a product based on customer needs. I am hoping to hone these skills that I have gained over the years and apply them to my career as a full-stack web developer and afford myself long term potential and growth with an organization that promotes good work ethics, values, and beliefs.

In short, my talents align well with your qualifications as I am proficient in the fundamentals of web development, building rapport, and most importantly, I can surely produce the project that you are seeking. I believe that I have the ability to accomplish not only what is required, but to excel and become an asset to your business. It would be a pleasure to have the opportunity to set an appointment and discuss this position in person. Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to hearing from you.

	cer	

Phuong Le

PHUONG LE

OBJECTIVE

I am looking for a full time position. I am a soon to be graduate from the Georgia Tech Full-Stack Flex Coding Bootcamp with extensive familiarity in customer relations. By utilizing my experience in web development, building rapport with clients, and dedicating myself to hard work, I hope to be an asset to your business.

EXPERIENCE

Prime Bar and Grill, Duluth, GA – Bartender

MAY 2019- AUG 2019

- Developed and prepared various drink recipes
- Accommodated multiple patrons with consistent customer service
- Prepared fruits, syrups, and spices for making mixed drinks each shift

A One Home Care Inc., Roswell, GA – Healthcare Marketer

DEC 2018 - MAR 2019

- Writing and delivering company presentations at various physician offices
- Worked as marketing designer by building company's website making advertisement brochures, flyers, etc.
- Provided Vietnamese to English translations from clientele to coordinators

Allconnect (Red Ventures), Atlanta, GA - Sales Representative

APRIL 2018 - JULY 2018

- Taking inbound calls and converting calls into sales opportunities
- Handling sensitive information such as dob, credit card, and social security information
- Setting up service for integrated companies such as AT&T, Verizon, Comcast

Umi, Buckhead, GA — Hostess

OCTOBER 2017 - MARCH 2018

- Answering phone calls and taking reservations
- Handling seating charts and organizing large parties
- Tending to customers over the phone for cancellations, alterations, and information

Jinya Ramen Bar, Sandy Springs GA – Server

OCTOBER 2016 - AUGUST 2017

- Memorizing food and beverage pricing, ingredients, and preparation
- Taking and delivering orders with punctuality and accuracy
- Engaging personally with the customer

5641 Roswell Road Unit 103 Atlanta, GA 30342 (205) 566-2320 phuonganh.leo312@gmail.com

SKILLS

Microsoft 365

Adobe Creative Cloud

LANGUAGES

English

Fluent writing and speaking

Vietnamese

Native speaker

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Javascript

CSS

HTML.

LIBRARIES & FRAMEWORKS

jQuery

EDUCATION

Peachtree Ridge High School, Suwanee GA — Class of 2015

2014 - 2015

Life University, Marietta GA

2016-

Focus: Dietetics

Georgia Tech Full-Stack Flex Bootcamp, Atlanta,

GA

2020